atchuup.com 2015-06-27

# Privacy Policy | Atchuup! – Cool Stuff, Pass It On

### Apr 04  
2014

 **[Atchuup](http://atchuup.com/)** respects the privacy of our visitors. This privacy policy shows you how we use and protects any information you give us when you use the website.

We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Rest assured that any information that you provide us when using the website will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

 **What we collect**

> Email address (for our newsletter, which you can unsubscribe from any time)

 **Security**

We are committed to ensuring that all your information is secure. To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to secure and safeguard the information that we collect online.

 **How do we use cookies?**

A cookie is a small file that asks permission from you to be placed on the hard drive of your computer. Once you agree, this file will be added and the cookie can help us analyze web traffic, as well as lets you know when you visit a particular website.

Cookies can help us improve our user experience and allow our web applications to respond to each user as effectively as possible, tailor-fit to each user’s needs and personal preferences by gathering information about their likes and dislikes.

We only utilize this information for statistical analysis purposes. We then remove the data from the system when we’re done with the analysis.

The bottomline is that cookies can help us provide you with an optimized online experience, by enabling us to keep track of web pages that you find useful or not useful. A cookie doesn’t give us access to your computer or personal information about you, except the data you choose to share with us.

You can, of course, decline cookies. You can do this by not accepting cookies or modify the setting of your browser to decline cookies. But this may prevent you from getting the most value out from the website.

 **Third Party Vendors**

> Third party vendors such as Google AdSense use cookies to serve ads based on your prior website visits.
> Google utilizes the DoubleClick cookie that enables them and its partners to serve ads to visitors based on their visits to Atchuup or/and other websites.
> You may choose to decline the DoubleClick cookie for online advertising by visiting the Ads Settings, or by visiting aboutads.info.

 **Links to other websites**

Our web contents contain links to other websites that you may also find interesting. Once you’ve clicked on these links and leave our website, please note that we don’t have any control over that other websites. This means we can’t be responsible for the protection and privacy of information that you provide to those sites. Always exercise caution and read their privacy policy first before doing any business with them.

 **Important note**

Atchuup may change this privacy policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to make sure that you’re happy with the changes. This privacy policy is effective from March 31, 2014.
